1800dentist.com 2007-10-20

# 1-800-DENTIST — We protect your information

#### Privacy Statement of 1800dentist.com

[](https://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.1800dentist.com) Your privacy is very important to us. As part of the normal operation of our site we collect and disclose information about you. This Privacy Statement describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. As described below, some of your personally identifiable information is used only by 1800dentist.com

#### Information We Collect

In our online find-a-dentist pages, to match you with a dentist, we require you to provide us with your full name, contact information, and dental need. In the course of using our site, we automatically track certain information about you. This information includes the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you go to next (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. Most sites automatically collect this information. 

In addition, we use cookies on certain pages of our site. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may be required to re-enter certain information more frequently during a visit to our site. 

If you send personal correspondence to us, such as e-mails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

#### Our Use of Your Information

We use the information you provide to return to you a list of up to three member dentists from which you may choose your new dentist. Additionally, we use personally identifiable information about you internally to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs. 

#### Our Disclosure of Your Information

Once you have selected a new dentist using our site, we send your name and contact information via fax to your new dentist. 

We have never sold, shared, or rented any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. 1800dentist.com cooperates with all law enforcement inquires. Therefore, local, state and federal law enforcement can request your name, street address, city, state, zip code, phone number, and e-mail address. Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Statement. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Further, we can disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. Therefore, although we use industry-standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private. 

#### Security

1800dentist.com uses industry-standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [info@1800dentist.com](mailto:info@1800dentist.com)
